I have to admit, I'm pretty impressed that you were able to find me.
It wasn't exactly my first time tracking one of you down.
I guess it makes sense I've gotten better at it.
Yes, but still, you weren't exactly easy on me, were you?
I didn't kill her. I held back.
Well then, what brings you here now?
I'm gonna assume you haven't come by for a tea party.
I have an important question for you.
Oh yeah? Go ahead.
I mean, I can't promise I'll answer it, but let's see, shall we?
Zoph Kiel is an angel who manipulates time, correct?
Also, each and every one of those twelve dials has a different kind of power.
So my question is, of the twelve, does one have a bullet that'll send someone to the past?
Just out of curiosity, what would you say if there was one?
That I want to borrow your power.
My, my. You're actually suggesting that I use you to bet for your sake? Is that really what you're asking me?
Yes.
Well then, here's my answer.
It's unfortunate. I hate disappointing people, you know?
You may be blessed with incredible power, but it means nothing if you can't hit me.
Uh-oh. I think I'm being rather underestimated right now.
Well, just cause I'm a curious kind of girl. What exactly would you be doing with you'd bet if I had agreed?
Simple. I want to go to August 3rd, five years ago.
Five years ago? Why though?
I have to go back there. I have to try and fix it so that my mom and dad's deaths never happened.
I'll change history. If you'll help me.
How interesting. I have to wonder, what is your plan if I choose to refuse you?
I'll make sure you agree. Any way I can.
Well, you've gone and said it now, huh?
Well, whatever.
As a matter of fact, I was a little nervous about using the you'd bet without having tested it out on anyone first.
So I guess I can just use you as my guinea pig since you asked so nicely.
Seriously?
Now, come to me.
Zavkiel!
Zavkiel.
Let's try you'd bet.
Go find out for me, little pig.
Prove to me how foolish it actually is to try and change the world.
And whether or not God permits it.
Ugh, Shido. I'm so hungry.
Wait a minute.
You're not going around giving our kinswoman the forbidden fruit before we get a piece, are you?
Complaint.
It would appear that Shido is unfortunately forgetting that he is our property first and foremost.
Hey! He belongs to me too, you know?
Yeah, yeah.
I'll grab you something, so hang tight, okay?
Do you two want anything?
Is that Yoshino's phone?
Shido, what are you...
Uh, no. Yoshino, this isn't...
What's all the ruckus when I'm trying to sleep?
No, this isn't how it looks, I swear.
Get off of her, you filthy pervert!
Crap.
Shido!
Gross, I can't believe you had the guts to do perverted things to Yoshino while I was literally sleeping right beside her!
No, it's a misunderstanding. I was just reaching for this.
Coterie?
Hello? Yoshino?
Coterie! Is that you?
I really made it. It's five years ago.
Metatron! Malak!
Yes, this is Tengu City's Nanku area.
Mom and Dad, they're so close.
Shido.
It's you. I found you. I found you! I found you! I found you! I found you! I found you! I found you! Finally, I found you!
Metatron!
Come on!
Exactly. Why did you attack me like that?
Oh, I see. So you've reversed the flow of time by using Zafkiel, have you?
That's surprising, that she would lend someone her powers like that.
Not so fast!
Oh, dear. Whatever the future me has done, it seems she's earned quite the grudge from you, hasn't she?
I'm sorry about whatever that was, but I'm afraid I can't let you kill me here today.
I have a wish that I have to make come true, just like you.
A wish? For real?
You kill my mom and dad, then you dare to have a wish in this world? Really?
Screw you! Screw you! Screw you!
I refuse to give you time to make your wish come true.
I don't even plan to give you any time to pray!
You'll die without accomplishing anything!
Disappear, leaving no trace behind!
You should have nothing but regret filling your cold, empty heart!
Nothing! Be gone from this world!
Wait, you think I killed your mom and dad?
I'm sorry, but maybe you have the wrong person.
Oh my god. Be gone from this world!
Oh my god.
uh
that was truly magnificent i never would have imagined you could wield metatron quite so well
the birth of a powerful spirit should be celebrated that's what i think what are you
that brilliant attack i'm so glad i got to witness it this is all happening so that my wish comes to
pass goodbye now it really is about time that i was on my way you stay here there's no reason to
not when i've already achieved my goal for the day
yes i saved them mom and dad
no please no
angel
there i am it happened just like before i couldn't stop it i'll never forgive you i'll kill you
i swear that i will someday i'm gonna kill you
oh i see so fraxinus was anyway i'm glad you're safe we're in ratatasker's underground base
you all really should come too once your pickup arrives i mean wait how is it you know where
we're at she know whose phone do you think you're on right now anyway oh right
sounds like they're there i can fill you in on the rest once you get here okay hold up one sec
the thing is origami
excellent work ellen your performance really was superb
no i took one too many direct hits surprisingly the enemy had some talented individuals with them
fascinating well in that case let's hope that a good number of them have survived wouldn't that be nice
more importantly yeah i know i know i didn't predict this though i guess that makes sense i mean who would
have thought that she would become a spirit ah it's such a pity too ike i'm looking at you and
you're smiling oops well guess you caught me so where is she now hard to say it seems like her
reactions suddenly vanished do you think it's possible she could have spirit wave suppression powers
is that what you're thinking too if she's a spirit then she knows she'll be hunted by us
so of course she would hide herself maybe that would undoubtedly be smart but the fact that we have
such trouble understanding their actions is what makes spirits spirits wouldn't you say
you never know she might actually be watching over us right now as we speak
i wonder is it possible that origami was able to achieve her goal in the end
because really if i'm being perfectly honest in my dark little heart of hearts i truly hope that
she's able to make that wish come true wow it's so not like me to say something like that at all
have you been out in the moonlight too long or what hey come on i don't have to be one thing
sometimes i just happen to be in a more charitable mood than others
what the hell's that
what what is it what the heck is happening out there what is this
a spirit but i don't really get it something this powerful without any warning
chotori listen this reaction is no normal spirit it's an inverse
are you okay shito yeah thanks toka but we have to save the other people everyone help me out k
that blast where'd it come from
wait or it got me oh no what the hell happened to you origami
origami tobiichi's a spirit listen shito you need to prepare yourself emotionally no matter who it might be
a spirit is a spirit you'll have to capture origami tobiichi yeah i know
i have no idea what's happened to origami but look if there's one person in this world who can bring
her back that person is you shito
yeah you're right
i'm glad to see you understand if you were about to whine and complain about being the one to do it
i was ready to toss you clean through the freaking sky
a pledge kaguya and i will guide you there right towards master origami
shito please go to her and open up her eyes however you can
hey now wait for me darling it'd be so sad if you were to forget me
look at me
yoshino
um i kind of think we should take care of everything on the ground
using zod kiel's power i have a feeling i can hold her off
i guess i might as well help out too since i'm here
after all this debris won't be dangerous if i turn it into cotton balls
not sue me
thank you everyone come on let's go now i'll lead us and open up the way
gotcha acknowledged
mild praise you're pretty good at this i appreciate that
be ready to go as soon as i draw out her attack
i won't last that long kaguya yuzuru ready leave it to me agreed let's go oh i think not
we'll have no children meddling with the inver-
shito rescue now rafael al nahar
it's a pleasure to see you again shito itsuka
well the feeling sure as hell isn't mutual
she's comparable even to princess back in the day
what a magnificent inverse
ike will be so delighted
screw you we're not about to let you take origami
barking at me like some stupid dog isn't going to accomplish anything here you know
be silent
ORIKAMI!
It's me, Shido!
Can you hear me?
Alright.
ORIKAMI!
Damn it!
What now?
I've gotta go back up.
Huh?
Fraxinus!
Looks like you really went all out.
Totori!
I wish I could tell you to pull back for now and retreat.
Unfortunately, I don't think we can afford to do that in this situation.
Our transport device is hanging in there, though.
So we'll go ahead and try sending you over to ORIK-
KOTORI!
KOTORI-
What is this?
My gosh, long time no see, Shido.
KOTORI...
What are you trying to pull at a time like this?
Oh, my. Could it really be possible that the great Shido has completely forgotten what my personal goal actually is?
At a time like this, you say? I mean, if you think about it, what better time is there, right?
I can't be expected to let an opportunity like this slip away.
I'm begging, Kurumi. Please don't get in my way. I have to save them. I have to get up there and save Origami.
That one's hopeless, though. Nobody's voice is going to reach Origami as she is right now.
And by that, I do mean no one, including you, my friend.
I wonder what she might have seen on her recent little trip through time.
Well, doesn't matter. I think I've wasted enough minutes standing around talking to you.
It's about that time's off-keel. Let's get this party started, shall we?
Oh, wait, didn't I tell you already? You're mine now, no matter what you try.
How did it not hurt? Hey, what did you do?
What indeed, am I right? A good question, but it won't be answered today.
Don't.
What do you say? I don't know about you, but I think our date is long overdue.
Cicadas?
Wait, shouldn't the buildings be destroyed?
This is Tengu City, right?
Miss Tamae!
Hmm?
Uh, hi. How exactly is it that you know my name?
What? Hold on. What are you talking about? It's me, Shido Itsuka?
Oh, wait, are you actually trying to hit on me? Well, that's very flattering, but I kind of need to go now. Sorry, have a good day.
I don't get it. That was her.
Kudori?
Don't waste your time looking. You won't find me where you are. I'm in a different time than you now.
What are you talking about?
Using Zoph Kiel's last bullet, you'd bet. I sent you hurtling back to Tengu City as it existed five years ago.
Five years ago? You take me back to where I belong right now! I don't have time to screw around like this!
Are you completely sure about that? Because the only way to reverse the disaster that's unfolding in the present is to deal with the younger Origami you'll find in the past.
Origami?
Yes.
So, you're telling me Origami asked for your help to go back five years and kill Phantom?
Yeah, that's exactly it.
But if that's true, why would Origami go inverse back in our original time? I mean, what happened to her when she came here?
Believe it or not, that's something even I don't know. It's your job to find out. And then it's your job to reverse it.
Now maybe you understand why I shot you with you'd bet in the first place.
Yeah, I do. But tell me something. Why would you do this? Why would you have used your angel for someone else to begin with?
I know, right?
If I had to say why, the simplest answer is that I want proof. Proof that it is somehow possible for history to be changed.
She knows that she's becoming the thing she hates, yet she trudges on. Crossing time, defying God. In the end, where will that road lead her?
Yeah, I do. But tell me something.
I.
You.
ずっとここで、君と二人で
夜空流れる
星を見続けたい
君と対供の約束をしよう
世界から私だけ消えてしまっても
気づかれなくていい
If I am still here in my heart
What new air
urchase up to you
quietly high-end